

#### **ABOUT ME**

Hi! My name is Priyadarshan Ghosh. I am a Web Developer, **Android Developer & Competitive** Coder. Pursuing B.Tech in **Electronics and Communications** Engineering (ECE) from AOT(Academy Of Technology) under MAKAUT and have secure 90.45% till 3rd semester. I choose this branch because I am for Robotics and IoT technologies. always wanted to work and have a wide range of experiences and also quite comfortable working on the following languages HTML, CSS, Javascript, Node.js, React.js, **Backend languages PHP and My** SQL, Codeigniter, MongoDB, along with C, C++, Python, Java, Firebase, Mapbox, Andriod app development, Arudino, WordPress, Tensorflow I have successfully completed 87 projects and a few no. projects under my guidance are on. Meanwhile, I achieved 16 awards from National and International software companies. I love to work on Andriod base and Web-based projects very accurately. I am a 3 Star coder in Codechef.I have completed more than 30 web Projects, and recently I Developing on my College Web-Magazine "Ingenium". My Two Android Apps

store". My Achievements are I have in the top 6th Position in India's biggest virtual hackathon our project is Running ATM, I also the 4th Position of TOI presents Lost Vote this hackathon is we develop a web app blockchain-based voting application. Recently we build an IoT project Voice control LED using Google Home Mini. I am an adaptive, quick learner, experimenting with JS, and believe in Teamwork, I have a positive attitude towards life, My hobbies are photography, coding and listening to music as well because listening to music refreshers my mind.

Uploaded in the "Amazon App

### LINKS

Website:

http://priyadarshanghosh.me/

LinkedIn:
https://www.linkedin.com/in/priya

darshan-ghosh-0a6274190/

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2 000

Twitter: <a href="https://twitter.com/way2priyo">https://twitter.com/way2priyo</a>

Facebook:

https://www.facebook.com/priyadarshan.ghosh.9/

arsnan.gno

Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/way2

<u>priyadarshan/</u>

LANGUAGES

## BENGALI

HINDI

ENGLISH

# ACHIEVEMENTS

hackathon(2020)
Top 107 participants in Indian super brain 2020 (cyber security)

• Top 6 participants in HACK IN

INDIA India's biggest virtual

- 4thPosition participants in CODIFICATION 2020 (State)
- 4th Position in National Level Cipherthon Hackathon(2020).
- 5171st Place in Google Kick Start 2020 Round G
   2705th Place in Google Kick
- Start 2020 Round H370th Place(World) 34th(India)

Place in Google Codejam 2021

- 207th Place in Google HashCode 2021
   4th Position in TOI Lost Vote
- Challenge in India(2020)Top 10 Position Alan Ai Hackthon
- \_\_\_\_

### Art of Deploying a Static Website(React)

**TECH BLOGS** 

https://priyadarshanghosh26.medi um.com/art-of-deploying-a-staticwebsite-react-853a88d0c46e

## PRIYADARSHAN GHOSH

WEB DEVELOPER || ANDROID DEVELOPER || COMPETITIVE CODER || OPEN SOURCE CONTRIBUTOR

serampore, Serampore, 712202, India

priyadarshanghosh26@gmail.com

## WORK EXPERIENCE

INGENIUM

CODE

Mar 2021 - Present

DIGITALOCEAN

Oct 2020 - Nov 2020 SCRIPT WINTER OF

Nov 2020 - Apr 2021

GIRLSCRIPT

SUMMER OF CODE Feb 2021 - May 2021 INDIAN CYBER

SECURITY SOLUTIONS Aug 2020 - Present Web Developer

Open Source Developer(Hacktoberfest)

Open Source Developer(SWOC)

Campus Ambassador

Open Source Developer(GSSOC)

## SERAMPORE UNION

**EDUCATION** 

INSTITUTION SERAMPORE 2017

SERAMPORE UNION INSTITUTION SERAMPORE

2019

ACADEMY OF
TECHNOLOGY

CLASS X

**CLASS XII** 

Bachelor of Technology

# SKILLS

**FLASK** 

Kolkata

2023

C C++

PYTHON JAVA

KOTLIN HTML

CSS JAVASCRIPT

BOOTSTRAP JQUERY

NODE.JS MONGODB

PHP
TENSORFLOW

EXPRESS.JS

MYSQL

CODEIGNITER

ALAN AI

WORDPRESS

#### HEWLETT PACKARD ENTERPRISE

**INTERNSHIPS** 

Apr 2020 - Jun 2021

JPMORGAN CHASE

& CO.

Jun 2020 - Jul 2021 MICROSOFT

Jul 2020 - Aug 2020

Software Engineering Virtual Internship

HPE Online Summer Training & Internship

Undergraduate & Masters Virtual Internship

Google Fundamental of Digital Marketing

# Apr 2020

Nov 2019
Intel Ai from the data center to the Edge An optimized path
Using Intel Architecture

Nov 2019
Ethics in Engineering Practice

Joy of Computing using Python

Indtroduction to Amazon Elastic Compute Cloud

Python Data Structures

Jul 2020 Python Data Structures

Aws Foundations

Aug 2020 Advance Styling with Responsive Design

Aug 2020 Interactivity with JavaScript

Dec 2020 30 Days of Google Cloud [ Cloud Engineering Track & Data Science and Machine Learning Track ]

May 2021 The Complete Guide to Bot Creation

Jun 2021 Introduction to the Internet of Things and Embedded Systems

Aug 2021 Java Programming: Solving Problems with Software

# Jul 2020

Sep 2020

Feb 2021

May 2021

**PROJECTS** 

Jul 2020 COVID 19 TRACKER

Aug 2020 Zoom Clone

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Zoom-Clone

Google Clone Using React.js

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/SKYPE-APP

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Google-Clone

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Doc-to-Handwritting

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/COVID-19-TRACKER

Oct 2020 Online Shopping Price Comparison Bot Using Python

cation

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Online-Shopping-Price-Comparison-Bot-Using-Python

Dec 2020 Blockchain based Online Voting Application
https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/TOI-LOST-VOTE

Jan 2021 Voice Control News Application

<a href="https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Voice-Control-News-Appli">https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Voice-Control-News-Appli</a>

Feb 2021 Doc to Handwritting

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Control-Website-With-Your-Eyes

**Control Website With Your Eyes** 

Apr 2021 DisneyPlus Clone

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/DisneyPlus-Clone

May 2021 Covid19 Vaccination Availability

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Covid19-Vaccination-Availability

https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/Object-Detection-Using-Tensorflow.js

**Object Detection Using Tensorflow.js** 

Jun 2021 SPO2 METER

<a href="https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/SPO2-METER">https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/SPO2-METER</a>

Jul 2021 React Native Food Ordering App

<a href="https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/React-Native-Food-Ordering-App">https://github.com/Priyadarshan2000/React-Native-Food-Ordering-App</a>

PHOTOGRAPHY, CODING, LISTENING MUSIC